Guide to the Lucy Maynard Salmon Historical Materials Collection, 1690-1982 (bulk 1790-1899)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES XX. Miscellaneous Items and Realia
  - Commercial Advertiser, New York, 2 Oct 1797 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Dunlap and Claypoole's American Daily Advertiser, Philadelphia, 19 Dec 1793 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Centennial Number Irish World, 1876 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Ulster County Gazette, Kingston, NY, 4 Jan 1800 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Albany Evening Journal, Albany, NY, 21 Jan 1838 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Cortland County Whig, Homer, NY, 15 Oct 1846 (Box 18 (Oversize))
  - Three French Broadsides relating to the Dreyfus Affair, 1899 (Mapcase - Drawer 33)
  - A facsimile copy of the Boston Gazette, 12 March 1770; [MISSING as of August 2007]
  - Carte de Kentucke, par John Tilson, Dediee a l'Honorable Congres des Etats-Unis de l'amerique et a son excellence George Washington, Commandant en chef de ses armees, undated; (Photostat) [MISSING as of August 2007]
  - Coin Collection, [MISSING as of August 2007]